{
    "subject": "resource/Daphne_Heard",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Plymouth",
    "human_readable": "Daphne Heard was born in Plymouth.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9831840395927429,
            "question": "Is Plymouth the birthplace of Daphne Heard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8440356850624084,
            "question": "Where was Daphne Heard born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7086935043334961,
            "question": "In which English city was Daphne Heard born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6042391657829285,
            "question": "Where did Daphne Heard come from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5932861566543579,
            "question": "What city is associated with Daphne Heard's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.571735680103302,
            "question": "Can you tell me the place of birth for Daphne Heard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.555030345916748,
            "question": "Which city holds significance for Daphne Heard due to her birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47631627321243286,
            "question": "What is the birthplace of actress Daphne Heard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40413275361061096,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Daphne Heard originated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3623638153076172,
            "question": "Name a place connected to Daphne Heard's early life."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Daphne Heard was born in Plymouth.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4731_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the city where Daphne Heard originated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4731_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the birthplace of actress Daphne Heard?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4731_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which city holds significance for Daphne Heard due to her birth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4731_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4731_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4731_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4731_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4731_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4731_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4731_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4731_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4731_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4731_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4731_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents indicate that Daphne Heard was born in Plymouth, Devon. Therefore, the statement \"Daphne Heard was born in Plymouth\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}